dialrequest.com 2014-11-23

# Dial Request-Beyond Search – Chennai's local search engine - Car, Bike, Mobile Dealer List in Chennai | Hotel, Restaurant in Chennai | Shopping Malls, banks in Chennai

###  PRIVACY POLICY:

Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy set out below. References to "we", "us" and "our" in this policy are references to Dial Request as appropriate. Dial Request is Biggest Online Search Multi-Directory. We provide information instantly to users and help them choose the best option available. Protecting your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used. We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time and your continued use of the Website will be deemed to be acceptance of amendments we make. 

####  What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out our form. When registering our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address and password. You may enter our site anonymously as well. 

####  What do we use your information for?

  * With the help of the information you provide, we personalise your experience by administering better responses to your individual needs
  * We continuously improve our website based on the information and feedback provided by you
  * We improve customer service by providing appropriate responses to your customer service requests and support needs
  * The information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or shared with any other company without your consent, other than the explicit purpose of delivering the requested product or service by the customer for process transaction
  * The email addresses you provide would be used to send periodic emails to you in order to keep you updated pertaining your desired request
  * The information will also be used to administer a contest, promotion and survey

####  How do we protect your information?

We contrive various security measures in order to safe-guard your personal information provided to us. 

####  Do we use cookies?

No we do not use cookies. 

####  Third Party Links

With discretion, we may offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have their own independent privacy policies. We are not liable for content or activities affiliated to these sites. We seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback from your side. 

####  Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy is subjected to the information collected through our website and not to any information collected offline. 

####  Terms and Conditions

Please visit our Terms & Conditions page that establishes the use, disclaimer, and the limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

####  Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

If you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies; please send us an email at [info@dialrequest.com](mailto:info@dialrequest.com)
